<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Medical Information</string>

    <!-- Medicine -->

    <string name="Acrocyanosis_history">Acrocyanosis is persistent blue or cyanotic discoloration of the extremities, most commonly occurring in the hands, although it also occurs in the feet and distal parts of face. Although described over 100 years ago and not uncommon in practice, the nature of this phenomenon is still uncertain.</string>
    <string name="Acroparesthesia_history">The condition was named acroparesthesia in 1890 and, in the following years, was accepted as a disease in medical textbooks. Almost all of the patients with acroparesthesia, described at the end of the nineteenth and the first half of the twentieth century, would today be diagnosed with idiopathic CTS.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Myocarditis_history">Patients with myocarditis have a clinical history of acute decompensation of heart failure, but they have no other underlying cardiac dysfunction or have low cardiac risk. The diagnosis is usually presumptive, based on patient demographics and the clinical course (eg, spontaneous recovery following supportive care).</string>
    <string name="Cardiomegaly_history">Cardiomegaly (sometimes megacardia or megalocardia) is a medical condition in which the heart is enlarged. As such, it is more commonly referred to simply as "having an enlarged heart". It is usually the result of underlying conditions that make the heart work harder, such as obesity, heart valve disease, high blood pressure (hypertension), and coronary artery disease. Cardiomyopathy is also associated with cardiomegaly.</string>
    <string name="Dressler_history">Not to be confused with DRESS Syndrome. <b>Dressler syndrome</b> is a secondary form of pericarditis that occurs in the setting of injury to the heart or the pericardium (the outer lining of the heart). It consists of fever, pleuritic pain, pericarditis and/or a pericardial effusion. Dressler syndrome is also known as postmyocardial infarction syndrome and the term is sometimes used to refer to post-pericardiotomy pericarditis. It was first characterized by William Dressler at Maimonides Medical Center in 1956. It should not be confused with the Dressler\'s syndrome of haemoglobinuria named for Lucas Dressler, who characterized it in 1854.</string>
    <string name="Acrodermatitis_Enteropathic_history">Acrodermatitis enteropathica (AE) is a disorder of zinc metabolism that occurs in one of three forms: an inborn (congenital) form and two acquired forms. The inborn form of AE is a rare genetic disorder characterized by intestinal abnormalities that lead to the inability to absorb zinc from the intestine.</string>
    <string name="Allergic_Dermatitis_history">Allergic contact dermatitis occurs when a substance to which you\'re sensitive (allergen) triggers an immune reaction in your skin. It often affects only the area that came into contact with the allergen.</string>
    <string name="Erythrasma_history">Erythrasma is a bacterial infection of the skin typically caused by Corynebacterium minutissimum. This pathogen infects the stratum corneum in warm and wet areas of the skin. Most commonly, the axillary, inguinal, and interdigital regions are affected.</string>
    <string name="Black_Piedra_history">Black piedra is a fungal infection of the hair shafts. It is also known as Trichomycosis nodosa. The fungal elements are attached to the hair shaft to form nodules along the hair shaft. It predominantly affects scalp hair, although involvement of the beard, mustache, and pubic hairs is also known.</string>
    <string name="Nevus_history">(NEE-vus) A benign (not cancer) growth on the skin that is formed by a cluster of melanocytes (cells that make a substance called melanin, which gives color to skin and eyes). A nevus is usually dark and may be raised from the skin. Also called mole.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Respiratory_Failure"> Acute respiratory distress syndrome (ARDS) occurs when fluid builds up in the tiny, elastic air sacs (alveoli) in your lungs. The fluid keeps your lungs from filling with enough air, which means less oxygen reaches your bloodstream. This deprives your organs of the oxygen they need to function.</string>
    <string name="Addisonian_Crisis">An addisonian crisis is a life-threatening situation that results in low blood pressure, low blood levels of sugar and high blood levels of potassium. You will need immediate medical care. People with Addison\'s disease commonly have associated autoimmune diseases.</string>
    <string name="Cardiac_Arrest">Sudden cardiac arrest is the abrupt loss of heart function, breathing and consciousness. The condition usually results from a problem with your heart\'s electrical system, which disrupts your heart\'s pumping action and stops blood flow to your body.</string>
    <string name="Diabetic_Coma">A diabetic coma is a life-threatening disorder that causes unconsciousness. If you have diabetes, dangerously high blood sugar (hyperglycemia) or dangerously low blood sugar (hypoglycemia) can lead to a diabetic coma.</string>
    <string name="Thyroid_Crysis">Thyroid storm (also called thyroid crisis and thyrotoxic crisis) happens when your thyroid gland releases a large amount of thyroid hormone in a short amount of time. It\'s a rare complication of hyperthyroidism. Thyroid storm is a medical emergency and is life-threatening.</string>
    <string name="Acromegaly">Acromegaly is a rare condition where the body produces too much growth hormone, causing body tissues and bones to grow more quickly. Over time, this leads to abnormally large hands and feet, and a wide range of other symptoms. Acromegaly is usually diagnosed in adults aged 30 to 50, but it can affect people of any age.</string>
    <string name="Addisons_Disease">Addison\'s disease, also called adrenal insufficiency, is an uncommon disorder that occurs when your body doesn\'t produce enough of certain hormones. In Addison\'s disease, your adrenal glands, located just above your kidneys, produce too little cortisol and, often, too little aldosterone.</string>
    <string name="Carcinoid_Syndrome">A carcinoid tumour is a rare cancer of the neuroendocrine system – the body system that produces hormones. The tumour usually grows in the bowels or appendix, but it can also be found in the stomach, pancreas, lung, breast, kidney, ovaries or testicles.</string>
    <string name="Cushings_Disease">Cushing disease (also called Cushing\'s disease) occurs when your body makes too much cortisol, a hormone related to the body\'s stress response. It\'s a rare pituitary disorder that is progressive. That means that without treatment, it gets worse over time.</string>
    <string name="Nelson_Syndrome">Nelson\'s syndrome is a rare disorder that occurs in some patients with Cushing\'s disease patients as a result of removing both adrenal glands. In Nelson\'s syndrome, the pituitary tumor continues to grow and release the hormone ACTH.</string>
    <string name="Abscess_Of_Liver">A liver abscess is defined as a pus-filled mass in the liver that can develop from injury to the liver or from an intra-abdominal infection disseminated from the portal vein. The majority of these abscesses are categorized as pyogenic or amoebic, although a minority are caused by parasites and fungi.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Gastric_Dilation">Acute gastric dilatation is the radiological finding of a massively enlarged stomach as seen on plain film X-ray or a computerized tomography scan of the abdomen. It is a rare entity with high mortality if not treated promptly and is often not reported due to a lack of physician awareness.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Hepatitis_A">It is spread when someone unknowingly ingests the virus — even in microscopic amounts — through close personal contact with an infected person or through eating contaminated food or drink. Symptoms of hepatitis A can last up to 2 months and include fatigue, nausea, stomach pain, and jaundice.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Hepatitis_B">Acute hepatitis B is a short-term illness that occurs within the first 6 months after someone is exposed to the hepatitis B virus. Some people with acute hepatitis B have no symptoms at all or only mild illness. For others, acute hepatitis B causes a more severe illness that requires hospitalization.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Hepatitis_C">Hepatitis C is often described as \"acute,\" meaning a new infection, or \"chronic,\" meaning long-term infection. Acute hepatitis C occurs within the first 6 months after someone is exposed to the hepatitis C virus. Hepatitis C can be a short-term illness, but for most people, acute infection leads to chronic infection.</string>
    <string name="Acute_Hepatitis_E">Hepatitis E is a liver disease caused by the hepatitis E virus (HEV). Although rare in developed countries, hepatitis E is widespread in the developing world. In the vast majority of people, HEV infection results in a self-limited, acute illness.</string>


</resources>